# MARIAM DARCHIASHVILI

**Graphic Designer** 

#### **ABOUT:**

Graphic Designer and Visual Artist, a graduate of KABK that is currently searching for a job. I'm a hardworker and (obviously you expect this in a CV) a quick-learner; with interests in typography, printed matter and curation, but always open for a new experience. My inspiration lies in music, senses, philosophy and dark aesthetics, which I always try to incorporate in my work both theoretically and visually.

Believer in power of black, reason and beauty of Classical Art

# LANGUAGES:

- Georgian (Native)
- English (Fluent)
- Russian (Fluent)
- French (Basic understanding)

## SKILLS:

- Honesty
- Fluent in use of most Adobe software, such as - Illustrator, InDesign, Photoshop, Premiere Pro, Audition and After Effects. Proficient in use of Glyphs
- Handy with techniques of Riso printing, silkscreening and letterpress.
- Intermediate use of HTML and CSS languages. As well as having basic knowldge of Unity and Blender.

## CONTACTS:

The Netherlands

+31 (0) 6 245 09 969 komnen.info@gmail.com www.komnen.com www.behance.net/Komnen

## **EDUCATION:**

# British Higher School of Art and Design /Art&Design Pre-Foundation

September 2013 - May 2014, Moscow

## Royal Academy of Art

/ Graphic Design (BA)

September 2014 - June 2019, The Hague, The Netherlands

## Stefan Schäfer Design & Research Studio

/Internship

September 2018 - November 2018, Amsterdam, The Netherlands

#### **EXPERIENCE:**

## FREELANCE DESIGNER FOR GD HOLDING

/Design

April 2018 - present, Tbilisi

## AMNESTY INTERNATIONAL - DUTCH 50TH ANNIVERSARY - GROUP EXHIBITION

/Design and Communication

April 2018, Amsterdam, Amsterdam Theatre

For a celebration of it's 50th anniversary, Amnesty Netherlands worked with KABK on creating a set of installations, researching and visualising some of their hardest cases.

## DON'T MIND THE WALLS - A POSTER FOR AN EXHIBITION OF KABK FINE ARTS

/Design and Communication

April 2018, The Hague, KABK

Don't Mind the walls was an exhibition organised by the 2d year Sculpture students of the Fine Arts Department of KABK.

## BITS&PIECES - A WEEKLY NEWSLETTER FOR KABK FINE ARTS

/Design and Communication

September 2017 - May 2018, The Hague, KABK

B&P is a weekly newsletter for Fine Arts students, that contains information of upcoming classes and events. Responsibility: design and sending out.

# KABK FINE ARTS OPEN DAY DESIGN

/Design

January 2018, The Hague, KABK

Design of the Open Day identity for the Fine Arts department and it's navigation. Included: event posters, exhibition information, navigational signs and same-day event flyers.

# CONSOLIDATING SOUND AND IMAGE

/Lecture/Workshop

October 2017, Moscow, Sfera Education

## VISUAL IDENTITY FOR SFERA EDUCATION

/Design

September 2017 - present, Moscow, Sfera education

## **BALANCE BY STRUGGLE**

/Curating and Designing an exhibition

September 2017, The Hague, Gemeentemuseum

Balance by Struggle - is an exhibition organised in the framework of celebration of 100 years of De Stijl movement by The Hague City Hall and The Royal Academy of Art. Me, Yeon Sung and Dominika Fojtikova conceptualised and curated an exhibtion in the walls of Gemeentemuseum. More details are online.